Stronger (What Doesn't Kill You)
压制:随Feng
更加强大(什么都不能击垮你)
歌手
Kelly Clarkson
You know the bed feels warmer
你可知道独自安睡
Sleeping here alone
床榻更暖
You know I dream in color
你可知我梦处缤纷
And do the things I want
又做回自我
You think you got the best of me
你觉得你拥有我最美的样子
Think you had the last laugh
你以为你笑到了最后
Bet you think that everything good is gone
确信你会心想我一败涂地
Think you left me broken down
你以为没有你我会垮掉
Think that i'd come running back
你还在想我一定会是那个不忍放手的人
Baby you don't know me, cause you're dead wrong
哦小子你想错了 你大错特错 因为我不是那种人
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger stand a little taller
那些没有彻底击倒你的东西只会让你更加强大 站得更高吧
Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone
因为傲然独立不表示我心孤寂
What doesn't kill you makes a fighter
那些摧毁不了你的困境 只会让你斗志昂扬
Footsteps even lighter
让脚步也更加轻松
Doesn't mean I'm over cause you're gone
因为此刻我明白你的离去不是我的终点
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger, stronger
那些没有彻底击倒你的东西只会让你更强大也更坚强
Just me, Myself and I
我只做我自己 从不依靠 从不追寻
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger
那些没有彻底摧毁你的困境只会让你更勇敢
Stand a little taller
站得高一点吧
Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone
因为傲然独立不代表我心孤寂
You heard that I was starting over with someone new
你听说了我已和一个你不曾见过的人重新开始
They told you I was moving on, over you
他们告诉你我已彻底走出你给我的阴影
You didn't think that I'd come back, i'd come back swinging
你想不到我的再次出现 会带着一身光彩
You try to break me but you see
你还想否认我的改变 但走着瞧 你终会明白
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger
那些没有彻底击倒你的东西只会让你更加强大
Stand a little taller
站得更高吧
Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone
因为傲然独立不表示我心孤寂
What doesn't kill you makes a fighter
那些摧不毁你的困境只会让你点燃斗志
Footsteps even lighter
让脚步也更加轻松
Doesn't mean I'm over cause your gone
因为此刻我明白你的离去不是我的终点
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger, stronger
那些没有彻底击倒你的东西只会让你更强大也更坚强
Just me, myself and I
我只做我自己 从不依靠 从不追寻
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger
那些没有彻底摧毁你的困境只会让你更勇敢
Stand a little taller
站得高一点吧
Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone
因为傲然独立不代表我心孤寂
Thanks to you I got a new thing started
因为你 我做到了抛弃过去重新开始
Thanks to you I'm not the broken hearted
因为你 我没有变成一个绝望的女人
Thanks to you I'm finally thinking 'bout me
因为你 我终于开始考虑我自己
You know in the end the day
你可知最终你离开的那一天
To left was just my beginning.....
会成为我新的开始…
in the end...
最终我明白
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger
那些没有彻底击倒你的东西只会让你更加强大
Stand a little taller
站得更高吧
Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone
因为傲然独立不表示我心孤寂
What doesn't kill you makes a fighter
那些摧不毁你的困境只会让你点燃斗志
Footsteps even lighter, Doesn't mean I'm over cause you're gone
让脚步也更加轻松 因为此刻我明白你的离去不是我的终点
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger, stronger
那些没有彻底击倒你的东西只会让你更强大也更坚强
Just me, Myself and I
我只做我自己 从不依靠 从不追寻
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger
那些没有彻底摧毁你的困境只会让你更勇敢
Stand a little taller
站得高一点吧
Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone
因为傲然独立不代表我心孤寂
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger, stronger
那些没有彻底击倒你的东西只会让你更强大也更坚强
Just me, Myself and I
我只做我自己 从不依靠 从不追寻
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger
那些没有彻底摧毁你的困境只会让你更勇敢
Stand a little taller
站得高一点吧
Doesn't mean I'm lonely when I'm alone
因为傲然独立不代表我心孤寂
I'm not alone
我不是一个人
压制:随Feng